Live from NPR News, I'm Giles Snyder. President Trump says that the U-S has delayed an attack
on Iran because Middle Eastern allies asked him to – Trump said his attack was going
take place Tuesday but now he's told military leaders stand down and NPR's Deepa Shivaram
a while because we've had very big discussions with Iran.
Cutter and the UAE both say a deal is close to happening, which
Is why they asked Trump To pause
The planned attack.
Trump says A deal will ultimately
have to include Iran agreeing
to not Have
A nuclear weapon Deepa Shivaram
And PR News
The White House President
Trump Had warned that
The clock was ticking for
Iran
strike a deal or fighting would renew. The special agent in charge of the FBI San Diego
field office Mark Bremley is asking the public for help
and investigation into Monday's shooting at San Diego County largest mosque
no matter how small, could be useful.
Police say two teenage suspects opened fire
at the Islamic Center of San Diego killing three men
The suspect were found dead in a car
with apparent self-inflicted gunshot wounds
A federal judge in Oakland California Monday
accepted juries ruling against Elon Musk
that jury deliberated less than 2 hours
and must lawsuit against OpenAI
And it's top executives
That Jury Found Open AI not liable
for having allegedly strayed
from its original non-profit mission to benefit humanity,
saying Musk waited too long
To file his lawsuit.
A strike at the nation's largest commuter rail network
has ended after three days
Bruce Conviser reports
that New York mass transportation authority
and Long Island railroad workers
reached a deal Monday night
Governor Kathy Hochul applauded
The agreement she said
MTA had reach the fair
Deal with five striking unions
Details of the agreement have not been released
but Hokel said it gave the 3,500 striking rail workers
a fair salary increase while protecting riders.
When negotiations broke off early Saturday
Hokele warned that
The Salary Raise being sought by
Unions would force the MTA to raise transit fares
perhaps as much 8%.
More than 250 thousand weekday commuters depend
on the LIRR
To get them into and out of city
This strike led
Massive traffic tie-ups
On Mondays
Would be Rail Riders tried
get to work by car. Notwithstanding the New Deal, Tuesday morning's commute is expected
suppressed. Mancione is pleading not guilty to state and federal charges
under 50 scientific researchers, and organizations are pressuring Congress
NOT to overturn the management plan for their Grand Staircase Escalante
National Monument in southern Utah from member station KNAU Ryan
Heinches reports. The group of archaeologists paleontologist biologists
And others called a nearly 2 million acre expanse an unparalleled living
Laboratory. They've nicknamed Grand Staircase the Science Monument because of its fossil record ecological diversity and cultural resources
The researchers sent a letter to federal lawmakers urging them
To reject an attempt
To toss out
Monuments Management Plan that governs science, conservation, recreation and cultural protection.
The effort is spearheaded by Utah Republican Senator Mike Lee who has long fought national
have sent to investigate the 1994 killings of OJ Simpson's former wife Nicole Brown and